

• Sleman, Yogyakarta

Fliw@digitalkode.com

🛄 https://fliw.github.io

SKILL SUMMARY

FRAMEWORK

- Laravel Framework
- React JS Library
- Vue JS
- Ionic

LIBRARY

- Bootstrap 5
- Tailwind

DEPLOYER

- Vercel
- Netlify
- Heroku

CI / CE

Github Actions

PACKAGE MANAGER

- NPM
- Composer

LANGUAGE

- PHP
- Javascript
- Typescript
- C++
- C#

DATABASE

- MYSQL
- MongoDB

MUHAMMAD RAFLI INDRAWAN

A PROGRAMMER

PROFILE

My name is Muhammad Rafly Indrawan, A Programmer and IT Enthusiast who domiciled in Yogyakarta, 21 years old, love coding from senior high school, already handle 35+ websites with 4 years professional experience. love challenge and new / strange things. currently focused on learning AI, especially machine learning.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lead Developer

PT. IDE JUALAN CREATIVE | May 2020 - December 2022

- Lead IT Maintance Division
- Implementing Kanban methodology on development
- Lead IT Research & Development Team
- Designing Application Architecture & Stacks
- Documenting Waterfall modeled Feature
- Documenting DDD type research module
- Automating QA and AT
- Interviewing & Technical Test candidate
- Code restfull API for backend Stacks

Lead Developer

PT. Naisha Inspirasi Muslimah | june 2020 - December 2022

- Lead Team Project
- Documenting Feature Design
- Documenting Timeline Waterfall per Backlog
- Create Dashboard, Front SPA & Mobile apps

Co-Founder

Digitalkode | april 2019 - july 2021

- Designing Application for Client
- Creating SaaS and one-Time payment project
- Pitching deck to many Client
- Leading IT Team creating Apps for Client

Lab Assistant

University of AMIKOM Yogyakarta | 2021

- Assistant in Laboratorium with Lecturer
- Teach Coding to college student
- Help Designing Module Practicum
- Check and Scoring College Student

ORGANIZATION

[2021 - 2021]

Lab Assistant Forum
University of AMIKOM Yogyakarta

[2019 - 2021]

• AMIKOM Computer Club University of AMIKOM Yogyakarta

PUBLIC SPEAKING

Speaker DSC Yogyakarta

 "Pre-Render Routes with react-snap" Google Developer Student Clubs

Speaker Startup Talk

 "Ultimate guide to creating a Perfect Founding Team"
Amikom Business Park

CONTACTS

• Email: Fliw@Digitalkode.com

• Whatsapp: <u>wa.me/628812671057</u>

• Github: <u>G</u>ithub.com/Fliw

Freelance Backend Programmer

PT. Gamatechno Indonesia | 2019 - 2020

- Assisting with senior programmer
- implement client's feature

Remote Fullstack Website Developer

CV. Oniversal Indonesia | 2019

- Designing Feature on E-Commerce
- Implement Feature on E-Commerce Oniversal

Remote Fullstack Website Developer

Telaga Nursery | 2019

• Create E-Commerce "kelengkeng itoh" apps

Remote Fullstack Website Developer

Capcuzz | 2018

• Design & Creating mini E-Commerce Capcuzz

EDUCATION

University of AMIKOM Yogyakarta

Bachelor of Informatics | 2019 - 2022

- IPK 3.7
- Peminatan Pemograman